<data>
   <news image="https://media2.s-nbcnews.com/j/newscms/2019_09/2770916/190301-richard-neal-al-1235_04e0a8e3e6792d34c204e8835ecbf5ec.fit-2000w.jpg">
      <headline>House Democrats prepare case to request Trump tax returns</headline>
      <description>WASHINGTON — The top tax-writing committee in the House is readying a request for years of President Donald Trump’s personal tax returns that is expected to land at the Internal Revenue Service as early as the next few weeks, according to congressional aides involved in the process. And Democrats are prepared to "take all necessary steps,"</description>
   </news>
   <news image="https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2019/01/MainYT1-1024x634.jpg">
      <headline>Trump says his remarks on Warmbier were 'misinterpreted'</headline>
      <description>Trump’s new comments, however, do not directly address whether he believes Kim bears responsibility for the death of Warmbier, who died in 2017 shortly  after being released from a 17-month stint in a North Korean prison. He had been sentenced to 15 years of hard labor after allegedly stealing a propaganda  poster while on a tour of Pyongyang in January 2016.</description>
   </news>
   <news image="https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2019/01/MainYT1-1024x634.jpg">
      <headline>Warmbier were 'misinterpreted'</headline>
      <description>Trump’s new comments, however, do not directly address whether he believes Kim bears responsibility for the death of Warmbier, who died in 2017 shortly after being released from a 17-month stint in a North Korean prison. He had been sentenced to 15 years of hard labor after allegedly stealing a propaganda poster while on a tour of Pyongyang in January 2016.</description>
   </news>
<news img="https://media4.s-nbcnews.com/j/newscms/2019_10/2775951/190306-school-of-rock-joey-gaydos-cs-932a_dfc4a4d19c3ebde303741f87ca81616f.fit-2000w.jpg"><headline>U.S. NEWS 'School of Rock' actor charged with stealing guitars</headline><description>On Jan. 31 in North Port, Gaydos asked a store clerk if he could play an $800 Les Paul Epiphone Prophecy guitar — and he did, before dashing out without paying, according to a probable cause affidavit prepared by Officer Ralph Casselli.</description></news></data>